<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Basics on SASS</title>
    <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basics on SASS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:40:09 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Sassy Css </title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:40:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 class=&#34;chapterHeading&#34;&gt;SASS/SCSS &lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p class=&#34;chapterTitle&#34;&gt; 
    &lt;ul&gt;
        &lt;li&gt; What is Sass ?&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;li&gt; Why Sass ?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sass</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/sass/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:40:27 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/sass/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt;Sass - Syntactically Awesome Style-Sheets : &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sass is basically an extension of CSS that adds power and elegance to the basic language.
CSS, though very simple to learn, it can quickly get quite messy, especially on large projects. Sass’ ultimate objective is to fix CSS’ flaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are two syntaxes available for Sass.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first, known as &lt;u&gt;SCSS (Sassy CSS)&lt;/u&gt; will be used across our examples, is an extension of the syntax of CSS.
This means that every valid CSS stylesheet is a valid SCSS file with the same meaning. Files using this syntax have the .scss extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second and older syntax, known as the indented syntax aka &lt;u&gt;“Sass”&lt;/u&gt;, provides a more concise way of writing CSS.
It uses indentation rather than brackets to indicate nesting of selectors, and newlines rather than semicolons to separate properties.
Files using this syntax have the .sass extension.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sass initially described a syntax of which the defining characteristic was its indentation-sensitivity. &lt;br/&gt;
Soon enough, Sass maintainers decided to close the gap between Sass and CSS by providing a CSS-friendly syntax called SCSS for Sassy CSS.
The motto is: if it’s valid CSS, it’s valid SCSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thats it about SCSS.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sass/SCSS vs css</title>
      <link>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/overCss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 18:40:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://replace-this-with-your-hugo-site.com/basics/overCss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;u&gt; Why Sass over CSS&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SCSS and SASS are the advance version of CSS3 (CSS),
These are their extension which allow you to write clean and quickly they are help tools for CSS language itself.
With these preprocessors you can write more reusable code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The point is not to turn CSS into a fully featured programming language; Sass only wants to help where CSS fails
So it simply adds a couple of extra features on top of it.
It allows you to use variables, nested rules, mixins, inline imports, and more, all with a fully CSS-compatible syntax.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will have a look at these features in the upcoming sections.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>